<!-- 
TODO:


-->

15.00:
Cooling tower has toggled transparency
Forge/crucible now smithing jobs
Smoker fueled by charcoal
Cooling tower can be filled with water buckets directly


14.00:
Removed torches - now in base game
Removed grilled wood meals
Reworked charcoal pit - now chars wood unattended
Increased coldstone battery fuel to last 6 days
Removed windows - now in CorePanda
Forge requires research
Charcoal pit has built-in support for bamboo and rubber wood if their mods are installed


<!-- Alpha 13 and lesser versions -->

v2.20:
Requires corePanda v13.3
Window can be crafted using glass or fused quartz
The forge can be upgraded to a crucible forge, allowing smelting recipes
Added recipe to craft glass at the crucible forge
Fused quartz recipe now only available at the crucible forge
Removed Stonecutting research prerequisites, since CorePanda adds ways to make simple stones
Lowered minimum artistic quality for weapons, since they are hand-crafted
Tweaked various small stats
Stuffed grill using metallic and stony stuff

v2.10:
Requires corePanda v13.2
Fixed cross-mod naming conflicts
Turnip_Full is no longer food, since its only use is to be destroyed
Windows require fused quartz
Added recipe for making fused quartz using the forge
Added copper to various recipe costs
Torches can be deconstructed
Fences no longer require diggable terrain

v2.04:
Added new graphics for glowstone/coldstone deposits
Reduced cost of glowstone constructs

v2.03:
Removed redundant inspect data

v2.02:
Rebalanced window lighting to be more realistic looking
Windows will brightly light 1 tile in front of them when exposed to full sunlight, useful for small greenhouses

v2.01:
Weapons no longer appear duplicated at smithing tables

v2.00:
Added CorePanda as a dependency, moved some assets (check corePanda changelog)
Added Coldstone - a cold stone that can be used to build coldstone batteries
Added Coldstone battery - cools rooms to below freezing, requires coldstone as fuel
Added Window - lets light in from outside

v1.60:
Added solar chimney for keeping rooms cool in the heat
Solar chimney requires rainwater and sunlight to function
Fixed oversized smoker icon

v1.56:
Increased hide bed comfort from 0.5 to 0.6 (only awful quality is worse than the floor)
Decreased simple door max hit points from 100 to 25 (existing doors will retain old hit points)
Increased grill fuel capacity from 10 to 15
Manual crematorium doesn't require wood to build
Decreased smoker cost from 150 to 100
Various small tweaks

v1.55:
Harvested turnips now drop turnips and turnip greens

v1.54:
Torches now forbiddable, won't be refueled

v1.53:
replaced missing base references
reduce torches heatpush

v1.52:
balanced torches cost/fuel; cost and consume 5 wood per day

v1.51:
grill, smoker, forge, and manual crematorium are now fueled

v1.50:
Torches and campfire now list their max heat provided (22/28 respectively)
Added grilled wood meals
Increased grill cooking heat from 0.1 to 0.3
Increased silver cost when building glowstone constructs
Raised buying price of glowstone
Added research to make grilled wood meals
Separated fences, crafters, and torches into different files
Added forge, forge recipes
Added bellows, a facility for increasing crafting time at the forge
Reduced charcoal pit crafting times for charcoal and yakisugi
Removed survivalists bow and shiv recipes (now in vanilla)
Bellows connects to char pit
Removed campfire, torches now last for 2, 4, and 10 days. Refuelable


v1.41:
Balanced cooking priorities:
  Cooks will now prioritize the standard stove over the grill.
  Cooks will prioritize the smoker over the grill and stove. This is useful since the smoker gives more meals per job.
Smoker sound fixed.
Smoker ingredient order changed so meat appears to be inside the smoker, not wood.

v1.40:
Fences require diggable terrain (dirt, sand, etc.)
Fixed charcoal pit graphic - really this time
Increased hide bed leather cost from 10 to 20
Increased hide bed wood cost from 8 to 15
Added Smoker, smoked meal
Redrew meal textures

v1.31:
Renamed 'prepared salad' to 'turnip salad', since the previous name already exists
Renamed 'glowstones' to 'glowstone'
Halved glowstone commonality
Reduced glowstone yield from 5 to 2
Slightly increased glowstone vein size
Reduced compacted glowstone glow radius from 6 to 5
Gave compacted glowstone a beauty of 20
Increased cost of pylons from 15 silver to 50 silver
Increased glow radius of pylons from 4 to 6
Glowstone constructs have a whiter glow
Lamp now costs 20 silver in addition to other ingredients
Remade lamp texture
Increased cost of torches to 5 wood per day - still cheaper than the campfires

v1.30:
PREVIOUS SAVES: If you have Charred Logs present on the map, you must either destroy or sell them before downloading this version to avoid any errors.
Renamed hide bed to bed, since it lists what it's made of already
Removed charred logs, torches now require wood
Torches now balanced at 80% campfire strength
   Increased glow radius from 6 to 8
   Increased heat push from 4 to 15
   Increased max temperature from 20 to 22
Torches highlight room to indicate they will provide heat
Torches moved to Temperature tab
Charcoal pit graphic fixed
Raiders now shoot over fence instead of always attacking it
Added glowstones - glowing rocks which can be mined
Added glowstones pylon
Added glowstones lamp
Added fence posts with glowstones

v1.20:
Torches give 5 beauty
Keffiyeh now insulates from cold by -4
Rebalanced turnip rotting
Added 10-day campfire
Added Charcoal Pit
Increased charcoal chunk stack size to 75
Torches heat push changed from 2 to 4
Added Yakisugi wood, yakisugi flooring
Increased cost of wooden vent from 10 to 20
Stuffed vent - uses Woody materials
Vent is now flammable, because wood
Made patch for VG bamboo charcoal

v1.12:
Fixed fence gate warning
Hide beds now show designation colors using pillows: green = colonist, blue = medical, etc.

v1.11:
Rebalanced turnip rotting to prevent an exploit
Reduced turnip yield
Reduced commonality of POW tribalwear
Added keffiyeh
Added 2 longer lasting torch variants with scaled recipes
Torches can no longer be deconstructed
Grilled fine meals require cooking skill of 5
Fences HP halved and made more flammable to better balance raids
Added Wood-Burning Crematorium

v1.10:
Added turnip plant, turnip, turnip greens
Added simple crafting table
Added recipes for survivalists bow, shiv, and tribalwear
Added salad recipe
Made wood more woody (enhanced bark graphics)
Added log fence, log fence gate
Added hide bed

v1.00:
Added Torch, Everburning Torch
Added Charred Log, charcoal log chunk
Added Grilled meals Meat, Veg, and Fine
Added Grill
Added wooden vent
Added Stump chair
Added Table(Indie)
Added Simple Door